i spring band and this installment of
我弹簧乐队和这部分
spring tips
春季小贴士
head and look at the programmatic
头，看看程序化
registration of beams feature the
光束配准功能
functionality in the upcoming spring 5
即将到来的Spring 5中的功能
release now spring 5 isn't due to be
现在发布不会因为 spring 5
released until summer of 2017 but
发行至2017年夏季，但
there's a lot of really great potential
确实有很大的潜力
here and I want to encourage people to
在这里，我想鼓励人们
try it a bit and kick the tires so to
尝试一下，踢轮胎，以便
speak and in order to do so we're going
说话，为了做到这一点，我们要
to take a walk down configuration lane
走下配置路
and look at some of the options and
然后看一些选项，
supported in Spring Framework up until
在Spring Framework中受支持，直到
now and look at this new approach that's
现在，看看这种新方法
now available coming in spring 5 so in
现在在 spring 5推出
order to do that we need to spring boot
为了做到这一点，我们需要弹簧启动
to that o which of course is in the
那个那个当然在
snapshots right now because it will
现在快照，因为它将
depend upon spring 5 now spring 5 build
取决于Spring 5现在Spring 5 build
on Java 8 so it features a Java 8
在Java 8上，因此它具有Java 8
baseline right as a result we can do
结果是我们可以做到的
some very interesting things when we
当我们做一些非常有趣的事情
define register applications with spring
用spring定义套准应用
so let's see what that looks like and
让我们看看它是什么样子
see how it plays out look we'll start
看看效果如何，我们将开始
our example today with a very simple
我们今天的例子非常简单
basically empty spring application and
基本上是空的Spring应用程序
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的是
strip back spring boot I'm going to just
脱去 spring boot
go back to low-level spring framework
回到低级的Spring框架
itself and we'll take a look at some
本身，我们来看看一些
very basic you know being registration
很基本，您知道正在注册
approaches some of which you may be
接近你可能是其中的一些
familiar with now oh if you've ever used
如果您曾经使用过，现在熟悉
spring before in the last 15 years you
过去15年中的春天
know that there's support for using xml
知道有使用xml的支持
applications configuration files and I
应用程序配置文件和我
won't bother showing that it's certainly
不会打扰表明这肯定是
still work it's still there it's fine
仍然可以工作，仍然可以
but what I'm interested in focusing on
但我有兴趣专注于
our ways to register being using java
我们使用Java进行注册的方式
codes right that's the the the thrust of
正确的代码就是
this particular spring tip so let's
这个特殊的弹簧尖端，让我们
suppose we have an application here
假设我们在这里有一个应用程序
right we've got two beans let's call it
对，我们有两个豆子，我们称之为
bar service and we've got another one
酒吧服务，我们还有另一个
called
叫
foo service and let's suppose that foo
foo服务，让我们假设foo
service depends upon bar sir so we'll
服务取决于酒吧先生，所以我们会
declare a collaborating object here
在这里声明一个协作对象
that's a thing that should be providing
那是应该提供的东西
the constructor and we have several ways
构造函数，我们有几种方法
we can tell spring about this
我们可以告诉春天
application let's suppose that this is a
应用程序，让我们假设这是一个
configuration application or
配置应用程序或
configuration class rather we're going
配置类，而不是我们要去的
to annotate it as such with add
用add注释它
configuration and let's say that we're
配置，假设我们
using just a regular application context
仅使用常规应用程序上下文
okay
好的
ultimately in spring we have the bean
终于在春天，我们有了豆
factory but bean factories just contain
工厂，但豆类工厂只包含
beans there are some primitives for
豆有一些原语
making it easier for developers to work
使开发人员更轻松地工作
with advocate you know in an application
与您在应用程序中认识的拥护者
there's a they called an application
有一个他们称为应用程序
context which in turn works with bean
反过来与bean一起工​​作的上下文
factories the application context
工厂应用程序上下文
provides lifecycle management so on so
提供生命周期管理等
we that tends to be the lowest sort of
我们往往是最低的
entry point into the spring framework
春天框架的切入点
these days and most people are familiar
这些天，大多数人都很熟悉
with that we're not going to use spring
这样我们就不会使用spring
boot for now we'll come back to that
现在启动，我们将回到
later and indeed if I left things like
后来确实，如果我离开了
this the result of this run method it's
这个运行方法的结果是
an actual application context right so I
实际的应用程序上下文权限，所以我
can I can I can get back there I can get
我可以回到那里吗
back the familiar ground fairly easily
轻松地返回熟悉的地面
but let's just do it the sort of harder
但是让我们做些困难
way right we're going to show
正确的方式，我们将展示
annotations or rather application
注释或应用
context EC equal new annotation config
上下文EC等于新注释配置
application context and what it's
应用程序上下文及其含义
expecting is a configuration class right
期望是配置类权利
so I'm going to pass in the
所以我要通过
configuration class here and that'll
这里的配置类
give us our first way of configuring
给我们我们的第一种配置方式
beans if you if you knew by XML you know
豆（如果您通过XML知道的话）
that XML provides a way to register
XML提供了一种注册方法
beans in a single artifact in a single
单个工件中的单个工件中的bean
XML configuration file and the bean
XML配置文件和Bean
definitions are Central's of all
定义是所有中央的
applications all definitions are in one
应用程序中所有定义都在一个
place and see that I sort of survey or
放置并看到我进行了某种调查或
at a single glance how things are wired
一目了然
together the Java configuration style
Java配置样式
gives you that same benefit so and it's
给你同样的好处，这是
also it very explicit right we don't
也是非常明确的权利，我们不
have to rely upon inferred sort of it in
必须依靠它的推断
front of relationships everything is
关系的一切都是
wired explicitly so I say full service
明确接线，所以我说全面服务
return new to service and I'm depending
恢复服务，我依靠
upon a bar service I can say bar service
我可以说酒吧服务
return new bar service now one of these
现在返回新的酒吧服务，其中之一
beans has a dependency upon the other so
豆对另一个有依赖性
we can tell spring to satisfy the
我们可以告诉春天满足
dependency by injecting the bar service
通过注入酒吧服务的依赖
like that or of course I can just call
这样，或者我当然可以打电话
the method like that either way the
那样的方法
results would have a food service that
结果将有一个餐饮服务
has the right collaborating object right
拥有合作对象的权利
so listen uh I tend to leave it like
所以听着，我倾向于离开它
this
这个
it's just server convenient if I need to
如果我需要，这只是服务器方便
copy and paste the definitions there
复制定义并粘贴在那里
so that's explicit right now let's test
所以这很明显，现在让我们测试
this code I want to test that this is
这段代码我想测试一下
actually working as we expect and that
实际上按照我们的预期工作，
we have two beans so let's go look at
我们有两个豆子，让我们来看一下
our test code here and we'll call this
我们的测试代码在这里，我们称之为
the context configuration and Tatian
上下文配置和Tatian
will tell us to use the config 101
会告诉我们使用配置101
application that class and I'm going to
应用该类，我要去
inject the application context by itself
自己注入应用程序上下文
here we go and here we'll say assert dot
这里我们去，这里我们要说断点
not no this time application time to get
这次不是没有申请时间
context beans who serves that class
服务那个班级的上下文豆
right so here circ wrong assert okay
正确，所以这里传出错误的断言可以
there are
有
there we go so there's that and thirdly
我们去那里，然后是第三
what I could learn assert that the M bar
我可以学到的东西是M条
service is not know so we have two beans
服务不知道，所以我们有两个豆子
one should be dependent upon the other
一个应该依赖另一个
and I want to confirm that they're both
我想确认他们俩
there as we expect right so far service
就像我们期望的那样到目前为止
that class and let's run this test so
该类，让我们运行此测试，以便
everything seems alright let's prove the
一切似乎都很好，让我们来证明
negative by them by saying that we want
他们说我们想要负面
this to be null right let's just make
这是空的吧，让我们
sure we're not getting some sort of
确保我们没有得到某种
fluke response and suppose in this case
uke幸回应并假设在这种情况下
it doesn't really matter but it's always
并不重要，但总是
useful to make sure we're not imagining
确保我们没有想象力很有用
things okay so we are running right test
一切正常，所以我们正在运行正确的测试
everything's working zurk not know very
一切都在做着，很不了解
good now
现在好
that moot that means that as far as
那个意思就是说
spring is concerned we have told it
关于春天，我们已经告诉过它了
about these two beans and they're
关于这两种豆，它们是
registered now this is a little tedious
现在注册，这有点乏味
I have to manage every single instance
我必须管理每个实例
thusly I can layer these together I can
因此，我可以将这些分层在一起
have one configuration class that
有一个配置类
imports some other config class right I
导入其他一些配置类我
can do that if I want I can compose
我愿意的话可以做
higher-order configurations Leslie but
高阶配置莱斯利，但
still I want to be able to only do this
我还是想只能这样做
kind of work if I need to why not let
我需要为什么不让我做些工作
the framework do the work for me
框架为我工作
whenever possible so for this we have
只要有可能，为此
components scanning right in component
组件在组件中扫描
scanning so that instead of explicitly
扫描，而不是显式
defining the into one with spring
用弹簧定义一个
implied relationships in those beans for
这些bean中的隐含关系
me by editing these beans with at
通过在
component and other such stereotype
组件和其他这样的刻板印象
annotation so this is a stereotyped
注释，所以这是一个成见
annotation it's got a role in the
注释，它在
framework itself and spring will use
框架本身和spring将使用
that stereotyped annotation to to just
那种刻板印象的注释
you know the term that this is a
你知道这是一个术语
component that should be managed right
应正确管理的组件
so let's revisit that test
因此，让我们回顾一下该测试
there we go there's our application
我们去那里有我们的应用程序
everything seems fine right so now we've
一切似乎都很好，所以现在我们已经
done the UH we've taken off the extra
完成了UH，我们已经完成了额外的任务
code we don't have to explicitly define
我们不必显式定义的代码
it d the fact that these beans are beans
事实是这些豆是豆
lives with the component themselves you
与组件本身一起生活
can mix and match right there's no
可以混合搭配，没有
reason you couldn't have a a bar service
您无法获得酒吧服务的原因
like so I turn the bar service and and
像这样，我打开酒吧服务，然后
then remove the annotation here for the
然后在此处删除注释
bar service here alright so in this case
这里的酒吧服务很好，所以在这种情况下
we should see the same result as well as
我们应该看到相同的结果以及
expected now they're pretty
预计现在他们很漂亮
straightforward purchased registering
直接购买注册
beand we can go a little bit lower
可以，我们可以降低一点
sometimes it's useful to be able to
有时能够
register beans based on some conditions
根据某些条件注册bean
or some sort of dynamic State so one way
或某种动态状态，所以一种方法
to register bean is to use the bean
注册bean是使用bean
definition registry post-processor
定义注册表后处理器
contract right so I can say public
合同权利，所以我可以公开地说
static class my ping dr PP implementing
静态类，我的ping博士PP实现
definition registry for processor and
处理器的定义注册表和
this callback this is that it's just a
这个回调是，这只是一个
bean I'm going to register being here is
我要注册的bean在这里
just a beam of a certain type but just
只是某种类型的光束
callback gives me a chance to register
回调使我有机会注册
objects that necklace right I'm actually
我实际上是正确的项链对象
going to register lower level types of
将注册较低级别的
the the underlying mechanism data line
底层机制数据线
sort of runtime definitions that spring
那种运行时定义
uses it something called a beam
用它叫做光束
definition so in spring gets all this
定义，因此在春季得到了所有这些
input from be it from beam definitions
来自光束定义的输入
or Java configuration or component
或Java配置或组件
scanning or whatever they all coalesce
扫描或其他所有合并
into a big bag big bag of bean
装进一个大袋子里
definitions and we can actually work
定义，我们可以实际工作
with that right so I've got a bean
有了那个权利，所以我有一个豆
definition registry here and I can
定义注册表在这里，我可以
register beans that's what you guys I
我要注册豆子
can say I want to register a foo sir I
可以说我要注册foo先生，我
want to register a bar so let's say I
想注册一个酒吧，所以说我
want to just register the bean bar
只想注册豆吧
service and it's going to expect a bean
服务，它会期待一个bean
definition and I can use the bean
定义，我可以使用bean
definition builder here so I can say
定义生成器，所以我可以说
generic generic bean definition passing
通用通用bean定义传递
in the the class that I want to define
在我要定义的课程中
right so bar service log class and I can
对吧酒吧服务日志类，我可以
say given the bean definition and there
说给定的bean定义和那里
we are there's my bean definition right
我们有我的bean定义权
so let's see if that works I'm going to
所以让我看看是否可行
go ahead and comment this out so now we
继续对此发表评论，所以现在我们
have no no bar service explicitly
明确没有酒吧服务
defined anywhere
在任何地方定义
save for this this a beam definition
为此保存光束定义
registry post-processor what I'm doing
注册表后处理器我在做什么
is I'm tapping into the beam definition
我正在使用光束定义吗
registry which is a lower level type
注册表是较低级别的类型
inside the Springs application context
在Springs应用程序上下文中
and I'm registering of being
我正在注册成为
programmatically giving it a beam ID and
以编程方式给它一个光束ID和
giving it a beam definition that these
给它一个光束定义
beam definitions are not actual objects
梁定义不是实际的对象
they ultimately turn into a reflection
他们最终变成了反思
code right code that's used in Santee
Santee中使用的代码正确代码
idea the definition and satisfied
想法的定义和满意
collaborating objects and so on
协作对象等
but there we go we've registered the
但是我们已经注册了
beam using the in other being definition
使用其他定义中的光束
registry post processor just to prove
注册表后处理器只是为了证明
that it doesn't work and I'll just to
那是行不通的，我只会
prove it we're not getting lucky here or
证明我们在这里不是很幸运
registered beam of the wrong type will
错误类型的注册光束
see that things fall apart so spring is
看到事情分崩离析，所以春天是
looking for that bar service and it's
寻找酒吧服务，它是
going to get that it's going to get that
会得到的会得到的
definition by creating a no argument by
通过创建一个无参数的定义
calling the new organic constructor of
调用新的有机构造函数
the bar service here naturally we can do
我们这里自然可以提供酒吧服务
more sophisticated kind of registration
更复杂的注册
so let's go ahead and comment out this
所以让我们继续对此发表评论
annotation here so that now we have to
在这里注释，以便现在我们必须
do both if to register both we can say
既可以注册又可以注册
register beam definition service and
注册波束定义服务并
here we're going to say beam definition
这里我们要说光束定义
registry sorry in red just being
注册表红色抱歉
definition builder dot generic beam
定义生成器点通用梁
definitions I'm going to say who serves
我要说的是谁的定义
and what I want to do is I want to say
我想说的是
that this is a genetic scene definition
这是遗传场景的定义
and I want to provide a certain type but
我想提供某种类型，但
I want also I may want to also override
我也想覆盖
how this object is constructed so
这个对象是如何构造的
there's a new feature in Java and spring
Java和spring中有一个新功能
5 which means based on Java 8 that takes
5意味着基于Java 8
a a supplier so what I'm saying is this
一个供应商，所以我要说的是
beam is of type true service class but I
梁是真正的服务类别，但我
want to define how this object should be
想要定义该对象应该如何
instantiated right so here I have a
实例化正确，所以在这里我有一个
callback interface using in Java 8
Java 8中使用的回调接口
supplier right and this Java a supplier
供应商权利，此Java为供应商
is going to give me the chance to to
会给我机会去
factory or build my in my particular
工厂或建立我自己的
beam so in this case I can say new food
光束，在这种情况下，我可以说新食物
service and then the question of course
服务，然后是当然的问题
is how do I get the collaborating object
是如何获得协作对象的
well this gives a little tricky right I
好吧，这给了我一些棘手的权利
need to downcast
需要垂头丧气
the beam definition registry into
光束定义注册表
something that will give me the the type
会给我那种类型的东西
I want in this case I want to say that
我想在这种情况下说
this is a beam factory right so sorry
这是梁厂，对不起
ping factory that caste passing in the
坪厂种姓路过
the PDR I want to get a collaborating
我想要合作的PDR
object in this case the bar service by
在这种情况下反对
type all right so I'm actually down
输入所有正确的信息，所以我实际上很沮丧
casting the beam factory and I'm using
铸造梁工厂，我正在使用
the beam factory to to resolve the
梁厂来解决
travelling objects and if we run this
行进物体，如果我们运行
everything should still work now
一切现在仍然应该工作
remember this beam factory is going to
记得这个光束工厂要
this definition here is going to be
这个定义将是
evaluated only when spring is trying to
仅在spring尝试评估时
factory the food service so it's at the
工厂的餐饮服务，所以它在
right point in time there's no work
正确的时间没有工作
there's not really any risk of early
真的没有任何早期风险
initialization problems right it's only
初始化问题就对了
going to call the supplier when it's
要打电话给供应商
ready to do that and so you can ask the
准备这样做，所以你可以问
context or a burning object accordingly
上下文或相应的燃烧对象
now this is all you know very very
现在这就是你所知道的
convenient and in this way you have a
方便，这样您就可以
callback interface you have it you have
回调接口，您拥有它
an opportunity here with this being
这是一个机会
definition registry port foster so
定义注册表端口培育所以
dynamically register a lot of different
动态注册许多不同
objects and here you get kind of a it's
对象，在这里您会得到一种
sort of Java like you're not dealing
像您没有交易的Java
with you're certainly dealing with the
与您肯定正在处理
low-level of the low-level beam
低水平光束
definitions and you're certainly aware
定义，您当然知道
of the fact that you're dealing with
您正在处理的事实
screen definitions and not proper
屏幕定义不正确
initialize objects but it's still very
初始化对象，但仍然非常
programmatic you get the communit test
以编程方式获得communit测试
this is very very nice now one thing I
这是非常非常不错的一件事，我
like about this of course is that it
像这样当然是因为
messes up the language so that's
弄乱了语言，所以
actually really convenient right look at
其实真的很方便吧
that and we can make this a static
这样，我们可以将其设为静态
import right so it wasn't a there's that
进口权，所以它不是一个
and when you look at that now the code
当您现在查看代码时
becomes much cleaner of course can be
变得更干净，当然可以
moved out of the blender definitions in
从搅拌机定义中移出
which case you don't even really need
这种情况下，您甚至根本不需要
that right the whole thing becomes a
整个事情变成了
one-liner really which i think is quite
单线真的，我认为是相当
nice so there's there's that that code
很好，所以有那个代码
is a much simpler to work with now this
现在使用起来要简单得多
gives us to the programmatic beam
给了我们程序化的光束
definitions or registrations our
定义或注册我们
application context here
这里的应用程序上下文
it's just down case it down cast it to
只是下架的情况下
that again now we can actually register
现在我们可以再次注册
beams dynamically and this is one of the
动态地发出光束，这是其中之一
really nice use cases is pure
真正好的用例是纯粹的
object-oriented sort of fun right so I'm
面向对象的乐趣，所以我
going to say register beam and let's
要说注册光束，让我们
suppose for now that I comment out our
现在假设我将我们的注释掉
being definition registry post boxes or
正在定义注册表信箱或
so actually that's before I run this
所以实际上那是在我运行这个之前
code let's comment that out and confirm
代码让我们注释掉并确认
that everything is broken okay so
一切都坏了，所以
everything's broken because I've
一切都坏了，因为我
commented out those two beans at the
评论了这两个豆
unit if that's failing I want to do now
单元如果失败，我现在想做
is I want to register beans with the
我是否要向
application context programmatically by
应用程序上下文
using the new generic the new registered
使用新的通用新注册
bean function the programmatic in
bean函数在程序中
definition and registration
定义和注册
functionality and spring five now I
功能和弹簧五现在我
could do that work on this application
可以在此应用程序上完成这项工作
context instance itself and that was
上下文实例本身，那是
certainly that would work but I want to
当然可以，但是我想
make it so that the code gets run at the
使它可以使代码在
same time as I am as my unit test right
与我同时作为单元测试权限
I want bill to make sure that my units
我要账单以确保我的单位
have sees the changes and remember the
看到了变化并记住了
unit test isn't going to run this main
单元测试不会运行这个主要的
method it's going to have its own
方法，它将有自己的
context and it's going to run its own
上下文，它将运行自己的
instant so we need to provide a
即时，因此我们需要提供一个
application context initializer so
应用程序上下文初始化程序
programmatic in definition initializer
定义式初始化程序
right and this is going to implement
对，这将要实施
application context initializer and the
应用程序上下文初始化程序和
in your sizer is going to instead work
在您的大小调整器中将代替工作
with subtypes of generic application
具有通用应用程序的子类型
context you know this generic
你知道这个通用的上下文
application context subtype here right
这里的应用程序上下文子类型
so what we're going to do is we're gonna
所以我们要做的是
tell spring to call this method when the
告诉spring在当
application starts up and there's a few
应用程序启动，有一些
ways to do this right there's a few ways
正确的方法有几种方法
to do this we can tell our our
为此，我们可以告诉我们
application when we run the application
运行应用程序时的应用程序
we can say AC dot rather we can say I'm
我们可以说交流点，而我们可以说我
programmatic of this and call initialize
对此编程并调用初始化
passing in AC and that would certainly
通过交流，那肯定会
work you know that's not a problem
工作，你知道那不是问题
but what we really want to do is to have
但是我们真正想做的是
this kid run uniformly whether we're
无论我们是否
doing the integration
做整合
whether we're doing this so I'm going to
是否我们正在这样做，所以我要
bring back spring boot I'm going to
带回我要去的 spring boot
bring back spring boot these two
带回这两个 spring boot
annotations are superseded at the same
注释同时被取代
at the spa notation provides the same
在温泉符号提供相同的
benefit really and then I'm going to use
真正受益，然后我将使用
the spring application runs nine to run
春季应用程序运行九个
passing in config 101 setup cache that
传入配置101设置缓存
class passing on the args and this
传递args和此的类
method here is actually syntax shortcut
这里的方法实际上是语法快捷方式
for new spring application and I'm going
对于新的春季申请，我要去
to add an initializer right so add
正确添加一个初始化程序，所以添加
initializers this is one way I can do it
初始化程序，这是我可以做到的一种方法
but this wouldn't be seen in my test so
但这在我的测试中看不到
what I really really want is just have a
我真正想要的只是
single place where I can define these
我可以定义这些的单个地方
incisors and have both the the main code
门牙，并具有主要代码
and the test code find it and that's
然后测试代码找到它，那就是
spring that factory's right so if I
春天那家工厂是对的，如果我
create my own meta instructor ii here
在这里创建我自己的meta教练ii
meta in create a new text file called
中的meta创建一个新的文本文件，称为
spring that factory and this is the same
春天那个工厂，这是相同的
mechanism the same service loader
机制相同的服务加载程序
mechanism that you may be familiar with
您可能熟悉的机制
if you've ever defined you own Auto
如果您曾经定义过自己的汽车
configuration right so we'll see
配置正确，我们将看到
application context initializer equals
应用程序上下文初始化程序等于
and we need to provide it a reference to
我们需要为其提供参考
our programmatic in definition of the
我们的程序化定义
initializer right so spring when it
初始化器正确，所以当它春天
starts up it's going to call this method
启动它将要调用此方法
let's just confirm that it does that so
让我们确认一下是否这样做
we'll say system dot air dot print line
我们说系统点空气点打印线
hello initializer right okay there we go
你好初始化器好吧，我们去了
let's run the code it'll still fail of
让我们运行仍然会失败的代码
course but we should see Hello
当然，但我们应该看到你好
initializer in there ah we need to
初始化器在那里啊，我们需要
restore our test as well so our pissed
也恢复我们的测试，所以我们很生气
is config one okay and we can say spring
是配置一好，我们可以说春天
boot test at this point that's all we
引导测试到此为止
need in fact we don't even need that
实际上，我们甚至不需要
remove it okay start again there we go
删除它好再开始再去
you can see hello
你可以看到你好
which
哪一个
hello initialize it right so there it is
你好初始化正确，所以有
it's it's certainly starting up spring
肯定是春天开始了
is seeing it in the unit test as well as
在单元测试以及
in the main code now it's our job to
在主要代码中，这是我们的工作
register programmatically the beans that
以编程方式注册
we care about so this is nice new API
我们很在乎，所以这是一个不错的新API
again Java 8 centric application back
再次以Java 8为中心的应用程序
context application context that
上下文应用程序上下文
registered bean and we can tell the type
注册bean，我们可以告诉类型
in this case we want to register a bar
在这种情况下，我们要注册一个酒吧
service class same as before that works
与之前相同的服务等级
just fine we also have this nice
很好，我们也有这个好
supplier base mechanism right so foo
供应商基础机制正确，所以foo
service class and then we just say that
服务等级，然后我们只说
want to return a new flew service it's
想返回一个新的飞行服务
going to expect a bar service well here
期待这里的酒吧服务很好
you know we could just use the
你知道我们可以使用
application context and get the beam
应用程序上下文并获得成功
like so so that would work certainly
像这样肯定会工作
let's try that right this is a example
让我们尝试一下，这是一个例子
let's see if that works ok tests are
让我们看看是否可以正常测试
green but we can actually make this even
绿色，但我们实际上可以做到这一点
simpler we can say bar service equals
简单一点，我们可以说酒吧服务等于
new bar service true service equals new
新酒吧服务真正的服务等于新的
service passing in the bar service and
在酒吧服务中传递的服务以及
really is the supplier for each of these
确实是这些产品的供应商
could just return the pre instantiated
可以只返回预先实例化的
references and now we don't even have to
参考，现在我们甚至不必
you know explicitly call into the
您知道显式调用
application from context if we don't
如果我们不从上下文中申请
want to for for simple code for simple
想要简单的代码
components that don't need certain life
不需要一定寿命的组件
cycles manager or satisfied before their
周期经理还是满意之前
reference right so here I'm the foo
参考权，所以我是foo
service has a direct reference to the
服务直接引用了
the bar service before anything else in
酒吧服务先于
the spring ecosystem and spring
春季生态系统和春季
application context if they had a chance
应用程序上下文（如果有机会）
to the post process it and satisfied in
对其进行后期处理并感到满意
dependencies but again it does read a
依赖关系，但同样会读取
fair bit easier and it's um it has a
有点容易，它有一个
benefit of looking like the code that
看起来像这样的代码的好处
you write in the unit test is you're
你在单元测试中写的是
mocking your libraries out right so
嘲笑你的图书馆，所以
let's see what that looks like now there
让我们看看那里现在是什么样子
we go so then the application has been
我们去，那么应用程序已经
started it's a it's registering to be
开始它是一个正在注册
dynamically now this mechanism it's very
动态地现在这种机制
powerful now we have the ability to with
现在我们有能力与
one bean with one object with one class
一豆一物一类
based on conditions or whatever other
根据条件或其他
dynamic state you have register one or
动态状态，您已注册一个或
more objects and here you've got actual
更多的对象，这里您已经有了实际
live you know live wire
活着你知道电线
these are not being definitions there's
这些不是定义，
no concerns about introspecting one time
不用担心一次内省
reflection metadata as opposed to the
反射元数据，而不是
actual objects you can actually just
您实际上可以只是的实际对象
work with the object graph itself and of
使用对象图本身和
course you can mix and match right
当然你可以混合搭配
there's no reason that I couldn't just
没有理由我不能只是
comment this out and then have the food
注释掉然后吃
service explicitly defined to get the
明确定义的服务以获取
beam from the application context which
来自应用程序上下文的光束
of course provides the definition
当然提供了定义
through some other mechanisms be at
通过其他一些机制
component scanning or Java configuration
组件扫描或Java配置
or the beam definition registry post
或梁定义注册表
processor so with that we've looked at a
处理器，因此我们已经研究了
few different ways to register beams and
几种不同的方式来记录光束和
with the application context we looked
与我们查看的应用程序上下文
at a few nice features in Java 8
Java 8的一些不错的功能
specifically the support here for
特别是这里的支持
registering a beam definition using a
使用
supplier and the support here in spring
供应商和春季支持
five for using the we registered beam
五为使用我们注册的光束
method also using a supplier right so
方法也使用供应商的权利，所以
thanks very much for watching and with
非常感谢您的收看和
that we'll see you next time
下次见